let ques = [
    {
        num: 1,
        question: "Who is the main Villain in Naruto ?",
        answer: "Black Jetsu",
        options: [
            "Madara Uchiha",
            "Black Jetsu",
            "Pain",
            "Sasuke"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 2,
        question: "Who is the Master Minder in Bleach ?",
        answer: "Aizen",
        options: [
            "Ichigo",
            "Yhwach",
            "Rukia",
            "Aizen"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 3,
        question: "Which Character Sacrifice his family in Naruto ?",
        answer: "Itachi Uchiha",
        options: [
            "Itachi Uchiha",
            "Naruto",
            "Sasuke Uchiha",
            "Hinata Hyuga"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 4,
        question: "What is best & Power Spell of all time ?",
        answer: "Time Manupulator",
        options: [
            "Gravity(Grave Anything)",
            "Time Manupulator",
            "Helling(Anything Can Hell)",
            "Summoning(Familiar Beast)"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 5,
        question: "Which is The Most Powerful Jutsu in Naruto ?",
        answer: "Infinite Tsukuyomi.",
        options: [
            "Tailed Beast Ball Rasenshuriken.",
            " Indra's Arrow.",
            "Infinite Tsukuyomi.",
            "Edo Tensei."
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 6,
        question: "Most Powerful Bankai in Bleach ?",
        answer: "Aizen's Bankai (Unnamed)",
        options: [
            "Yamamoto's Zanka no Tachi",
            "Aizen's Bankai (Unnamed)",
            "Katen Kyokotsu Karamatsu Shinju",
            "Satsu Karagara Shigarami No Suj"
        ]
    },
    {    num: 7,
        question: "What is the hair color of Naruto ?",
        answer: "Yellow",
        options: [
            "Black",
            "Yellow",
            "Brown",
            "Orange"
        ]
    },
    {    num: 8,
        question: "How many leaf in Asta's Grimoire ?",
        answer: "5",
        options: [
            "6",
            "4",
            "5",
            "3"
        ]
    },
    {    num: 9,
        question: "What was most Ghoul want ?",
        answer: "Human Flesh",
        options: [
            "Money",
            "Power",
            "Peace",
            "Human Flesh"
        ]
    },
    {    num: 10,
        question: "Remove one Anime in the list ?",
        answer: "I Can't üê∏",
        options: [
            "Naruto",
            "Demon Slayer",
            "Death Note",
            "I Can't üê∏"
        ]
    },
]